Finding Aid for Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies (University of Michigan) Records, 1892-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Program Evaluation (Digital Files)
  - Program Evaluations, (Digital Files), 1989-2006; .ZIP file
    - Program Reviews
      - Mechanical Engineering, 2006
      - Near Eastern Studies, 2006
      - Psychology, 2006
      - Sociology, 2006
    - Proposal for PhD in Public Policy and Social Science, 2000-Section I
    - Public Health Nursing Ms-Hsma Ms-Mph Program Proposal, 3-15-2000
    - School of Education Higher Ed Symposium, 1-12-2007
    - School of Natural Resources and Environment
      - Block Grant, 1-13-2005
      - Block Grant, 1-23-1998
      - Block Grant, 1-24-2007
      - Chairs and Directors Program Survey, 10-25-1995
      - Meldi Agreement, 10-20-2005
      - MS Changes EB Response, 11-1-2005
      - Program Proposal, 2-9-1994
      - Program Proposal, 6-1-2006
      - Program Proposal, 6-27-2005
      - Programs, 11-12-2002
      - Quality Assessment, 10-21-2005
      - Rackham Academic Department Profile, 11-17-1995
      - Rackham Academic Department Profile, 12-13-1995
      - Rackham Funding, 1-19-2007
      - Rackham Funding, 9-16-1991
      - Rackham Student Support Of QPQV, 3-23-1999
      - Rackham Student Support, 3-23-1999
      - Rmf Discussion, 2-4-2000
      - Rmf History, 10-5-2005
      - School Name Change, 6-17-1992
      - School Name Change, 7-22-1992
      - Survey on Environmental Studies, 10-1-1991
      - Travel Funds, 7-9-1999
    - School of Public Health
      - Population Planning and International Health Doc Students, 4-1-1993
      - Population Planning and International Health Program Director, 12-14-1993
      - Population Planning and International Health Request, 4-12-1993
      - Population Planning and International Health Review Committee, 5-6-1993
    - SJTU Transfer Credit Policies, 5-21-2002
    - Support ESS, 10-4-2007
    - Urge To Appoint Director Of Graduate Program Immunology, 12-29-1998
- Archived Rackham Graduate School Website
  The he Rackham School of Graduate Studies Archived Website series documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the Rackham School of Graduate Studies. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as newsletters and course catalogs), and information about admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, faculty, and the overall mission of the School. The website series is arranged chronologically and includes content captured by the Internet Archive starting in 1997 as well as versions preserved by the Bentley Library in 2002 and 2003. Starting in 2010, versions of the Rackham School website will be captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives (available at http://webarchives.cdlib.org/a/universityofmichigan/).
  - Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies
    - 1997-2014
      (These versions were preserved by the Internet Archive and are made available through its Wayback Machine. The Bentley Historical Library is not involved in the collection or maintenance of this material.)
    - May 15, 2002, .ZIP file
    - June 22, 2003, .ZIP file
    - Archived Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies home page, 2010-2014
  - Archived websites related to the Rackham School of Graduate Studies, 2010-[ongoing]
The Faculty International Grants (Box 137) and Faculty Grants are listed simply by grant number in the contents list of this finding aid. The following indexes, arranged by grant number, list the faculty member and department.
Index to Faculty International Grants (Box 137)
Grant Number Faculty Member Department
135053 Ness, Gayl D. Center for Population Planning
135054 Jourdian, George Arthritis Research Unit
135055 Simmons, Ruth Center for Population Planning
135056 Meisler, Miriam Human Genetics
135057 Yang, Wen-Jei Engineering and Applied Mechanics
135058 Knoll, G.F. Nuclear Engineering
135059 Wright, Henry T. Museum of Anthropology
135060 missing
135061 Olson, Gary Psychology
135062 Barlow, Robin Economics
135063 Medlin, William Education
135064 Spink, Walter History of Art
135065 Lopez-Grigera, L. Romance Language and Literature
135066 Hickey, Tom Institute of Gerontology
135067 Polakowski, K. Landscape Architecture
135068 Moll, Patricia Epidemiology
135069 Erickson, Robert Human Genetics
135070 missing
135071 Adams, Julian Biological Sciences
135072 Bashshur, Rashid Medical Care Organization
135073 Bernstein, I.A. Env/Ind. Health/Biological Chem.
135074 Lohr, Lawrence L. Chemistry
135075 Segel, Leonard Mechanical Engineering/Applied Mechanics
135076 Flannery/Parsons Museum of Anthropology
135077 Shy, John History
135078 Gosling, L.A. Geography
135079 Menlo, Allen Education
135080 missing
135081 Marans, Robert W. ISR
135082 Becker, Judith Musicology
135083 Tilly, Louise History
135084 Tilly, Charles Sociology
135085 Barnes, Burton Natural Resources
135086 Savageau, Michael Immunology/Microbiology
135087 Schwartz, Jessica Physiology
135088 Farrand, William Geological Sciences
135089 Kopelman, Raoul Chemistry
135090 missing
135091 Wylie, E.B. Civil Engineering
135092 Abernach, Joel D. IPPS
135093 Radin, Norma Social Work
135094 Edington, D.W. Physical Education
135095 Feldt, Allan Architecture and Urban Planning
135096 Langton, Kenneth Political Science
135097 Norris, Margot English
135098 Wotring, Linda Medicinal Chemistry
135099 Bronstein, Paul M. Psychology
135100 missing
135101 Frasch, Wayne D. Biological Sciences
135102 Richardson, Bruce Internal Medicine
135103 Simpson, Robert Pharmacology
135104 Bernstein, Isadore Environmental and Industrial Health
135105 Gans, Carl Biological Sciences
135106 Nanda, Surender School of Dentistry
135107 Lawton, Richard Chemistry
135108 Estabrook, George Biological Sciences
135109 Faulkner, John Physiology
135110 missing
135111 Reiff, Guy Physical Education
135112 Pollack, Henry Geological Sciences
135113 Meyers, Philip Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences
135114 Lewis, Robert Physics
135115 Maple, Frank Social Work
135116 Butler, Irene Health Planning and Administration
135117 Lin, Yi-Guang CRLT
135118 McKeachie, Wilbert Psychology
135119 Tilly, Charles Center for Research on Social Organizations
135120 missing
135121 Napoli, Donna Jo Linguistics
135122 Skolimowski, Henryk Engineering Humanities
135123 Carlson, Bruce Anatomy and Cell Biology
135124 Doneen, Byron Biological Sciences
135125 Higashi, Gene I. Epidemiology
135126 Nair, Madhavan Pediatrics
135127 Wright, Steven Civil Engineering
135128 Einhorn, Martin Physics
135129 Katapodes, Nikolas Civil Engineering
135130 missing
135131 Duke, Richard Urban Planning
135132 Simonds, Scott HB/HE
135133 Bogin, Barry Anthropology
135134 Sarri, Rosemary Social Work
135135 Adiv, Aaron Urban Planning
135136 Schelle, Robert Landscape Architecture
135137 Allen, Richard Communications
135138 Dressman, Jennifer Pharmacy
Index to Faculty Research Grants (Box 137-139)
Grant Number Faculty Member Department
386000 Geyer, Michael History
386001 Lindner, Rudi Paul History
386002 Rosenberg, William History
386003 Trautmann, Thomas History
386004 missing
386005 Crump, James Far East Language & Literature
386006 Hook, Peter E. Linguistics
386007 Kucich, John English
386008 Perlove, Shelley History of Art
386009 Sparling, Peter Dance
386010 Zirbes, Georgette School of Art
386011 Berridge, Kent C. Psychology
386012 Foster, Carol M. Pediatrics/Communicable Diseases
386013 Marrs, Carl F. Epidemiology
386014 Robinson, Terry Psychology
386015 Schwartz, Jessica Physiology
386016 Shapiro, David N. Pediatrics
386017 Cole, Robert Architecture
386018 Boronson, Todd A. Astronomy
386019 Dawe, Loretta J. Physics and Engineering
386020 Jha, Miraj Kumar EECS
386021 Pierre, Christophe Mechanical Engineering
386022 Rao, Ravi S. Mechanical Engineering
386023 Tickle, Robert S. Physics
386024 van der Pluijm, B. Geological Sciences
386025 Yagle, Andrew E. EECS
386026 Ziff, Robert M. Chemical Engineering.
386027 Barbarin, Oscar A. Social Work
386028 Hawes, Gary A. Political Science
386029 Howell, Joel D. Internal Medicine
386030 Jones, Carol A. Natural Resources
386031 Juni, Jack E. Internal Medicine
386032 Lieberman, Victor History
386033 Linderman, Gerald History
386034 Miron, Jeffrey A. Economics
386035 Scheppele, Kim L. Political Science
386036 DeYoung, Bill Dance
386037 Fogel, Jessica Dance
386038 Mannheim, Bruce Anthropology
386039 Mignolo, Walter Romance Languages
386040 Raiselis, Richard Art
386041 missing
386042 Doneen, Byron A. Biological Sciences
386043 Fleisher, David Pharmacy
386044 Frasch, Wayne D. Biology
386045 Greenberg, Miriam Biological Chemistry
386046 Meisler, Miriam H. Biological Chemistry
386047 Snider, A. Rebecca Pediatrics
386048 Yang, Victor C. Pharmacy
386049 Akerlof, Carl W. Physics
386050 Azimi-Sadjadi, M.R. EECS
386051 Baru, Chaitanya EECS
386052 Brown, April S. EECS
386053 Gidley, David W. Physics
386054 Mishra, Umesh K. EECS
386055 Olson, Lorraine Mechanical Engineering
386056 Pan, Jwo Mechanical Engineering
386057 Papanastiasiou, A. Chemical Engineering
386058 Talley, Douglas G. Mechanical Engineering
386059 Tryggvason, Gretar Mechanical Engineering
386060 Adams, Julian Biology
386061 Borenstein, S. Economics
386062 Shapiro, Vivian Social Work
386063 Anderson, Andrew Romance Language
386064 Baird, Kenneth W. Art
386065 Cole, Robert Architecture
386066 Isaacson, Joel Art History
386067 Makin, Michael Slavic Language
386068 Stewart, Paul L. Art
386069 Boehnke, Michael Biostatistics
386070 Bronstein, Paul M. Psychology
386071 Fisher, Linda E. Natural Sciences
386072 Gest, Thomas R. Anatomy and Cell Biology
386073 Kuwada, John Y. Biology
386074 Mychajlonka, Myron Natural Sciences
386075 Pike, Marilyn Internal Medicine
386076 Richardson, Rudy Toxicology/Biological Gerontology
386077 Worringham, C. Kinesiology
386078 Belisle, Claude Statistics
386079 Coffin, C.T. Physics
386080 Comninou, Maria ME and AM
386081 Grant, David R. Math
386082 Hansen/Robertson Civil Eng.
386083 Lafortune, S. EECS
386084 Olsen, Lorraine ME and AM
386085 Ringseth, Paul F. Math
386086 Srinivasan, M. IOE
386087 Stein, Jeffrey ME and AM
386088 Teitelbaum, Jeremy Math
386089 Barsky, Robert B. Economics
386090 Gass, Susan M. English
386091 Hilton, James L. Psychology
386092 Kennedy, Michael Sociology
386093 Lam, David A. Economics
386094 Mackie-Mason, J. Economics
386095 Miron, Jeffrey A. Economics
386096 Dworkin, Steven Romance Language
386097 Dwyer, Charles M. Art
386098 Lytinen, Steven L. EECS
386099 Marinaro, Louis Art
386100 Monson, Dale E. Music
386101 Schaum, Melita C. Humanities
386102 Seidler, Ingo German
386103 Udow, Michael Music
386104 Caruso, Rita Environmental/Industrial Health
386105 Clarke, Michael Internal Medicine
386106 Dixit, Vishva M. Pathology
386107 Fogel, Robert Herbarium
386108 McKitrick, Mary Biology
386109 Nussbaum, Ronald Zoology, Museum of
386110 Remick, Daniel Pathology
386111 Rogers, Ann E. Medical/Surgical Nursing
386112 Sporn, Peter Internal Medicine
386113 Tsubota, Stuart Biology
386114 Kabamba, Pierre Aerospace Engineering
386115 Penner-Hahn, J. Chemistry
386116 Schunck, Brian EECS
386117 Crow, Thomas History of Art
386118 Dauser, Robert Neurosurgery
386119 Bound, John Economics
386120 Kahn, Peggy Political Science
386121 Tonomura, Hitomi History
386122 VanHook, Mary Social Work
386123 Whatley, Warren Economics
386124 Alexander, William English
386125 Delbanco, Nicholas English
386126 Harding, Susan Anthropology
386127 Kibbie, James Music
386128 Lawler, John M. Linguistics
386129 Markey, Thomas German
386130 Moldenhauer, J. Art
386131 Overmyer, Dwayne Art
386132 Pijanowski, Hiroko Art
386133 Porter, James Classical Studies
386134 Braun, Daniel K. Internal Medicine
386135 Chauncey, James B. Internal Medicine
386136 Foster, Norman Neurology
386137 Glorioso, Joseph ULAM/Microbiology/Immunology
386138 Lawrence, Theodore Radiation Oncology
386139 Lombardo, Michael Biology
386140 Pichersky, Eran Biology
386141 Raper, Steven E. Surgery
386142 Thiele, Dennis J. Biochemistry
386143 Borgers, C. Mathematics
386144 Bothun, Gregory Astronomy
386145 Brereton, Giles J. Mechanical Engineering
386146 Dahm, Werner J.A. Aerospace Engineering
386147 Fassois, S. Mechanical Engineering
386148 Gaskell, C. Martin Astronomy
386149 Lott, John W. Mathematics
386150 missing
386151 Summerfield,G. Nuclear Engineering
386152 Cole, Juan R.I. History
386153 Danziger, Sandra Social Work
386154 Jones, Carol A. Econ/Natural Resources
386155 Perry, Michelle Psychology
386156 Watkins, Bruce Sports Management
386157 Pierce, Penny R. Nursing
386158 Berry, Paul Allan History of Art
386159 Carpenter, Bogdana Slavic Language
386160 Cheng, Mignonette Art
386161 Dwork, Deborah Public Health
386162 Eley, Geoffrey History
386163 Anderson-Levitt,K. Behavioral Science
386164 Cease, Kemp B. Internal Medicine
386165 Goldberg, Deborah Biology
386166 Jenista, Jerri Pediatrics
386167 missing
386168 Loubert, Peter Kinesiology
386169 Maybaum, Jonathan Pharmacology
386170 Schoeppel, Sonja Radiation Oncology
386171 Smuts, Barbara Psychology/Anthropology
386172 Sowers, MaryFran Epidemiology
386173 Zolan, Miriam Natural Sciences
386174 Axelrod, Daniel Physics
386175 Knochel, Paul Chemistry
386176 Kuczkowski, Robert Chemistry
386177 Perkins, Noel C. Mechanical Engineering
386178 Ravishankar, C. EECS
386179 Ryan, Robert R. Mechanical Engineering
386180 Sanders, T.M. Physics
386181 Bogin, Barry Behavioral Sciences
386182 Bound, John Economics
386183 Crystal, Jill Political Science
386184 Humphreys, Sarah History
386185 Mangelsdorf, Sarah Psychology
386186 Bahti, Timothy Germanic Language
386187 Brown, Raelinda Music
386188 missing
386189 Fries, Marilyn Germanic Language
386190 Jackson, Marion E. Art
386191 Ormand, Fred Music
386192 Rosenberg, Richard Music
386193 Sarath, Edward Music
386194 Szatrowski, Polly Asian Language
386195-387900 missing
387901 Winn, James A. English
387902 Beaver, Frank Communications
387903 Rush, Jon Art
387904 Hilbish, Thomas Music
387905 Borders, James M. Music
387906 Kyes, Robert German Language/Literature
387907 Erickson, Robert Human Genetics
387908 Goldstein, Steven Surgery
387909 Hutchinson, R. Pediatrics
387910 missing
387911 Joseph, Jill Epidemiology
387912 Bhattacharya, P. Electrical/Computer Engineering
387913 Breitenbach, J. Electrical/Computer Engineering
387914 Hass, Joel Mathematics
387915 Ramanathan, J. Mathematics
387916 Blouin, Francis X. Library Science
387917 Eldersveld, Samuel Political Science
387918 Feldman, Martha Political Science
387919 Gitelman, Ziv Political Science
387920 missing
387921 Goldenberg, Edie Political Science
387922 Kamachi, Noriko Social Sciences
387923 Meyers, Judith Psychology
387924 Price, Jacob History
387925 Rauma, David Sociology
387926 Wolpoff, Milford Anthropology
387927 Olson, Judith Computer/Information Systems
387928 Dworkin, Steven Romance Languages
387929 Ellison, Julie English
387630 missing
387931 Hatten, Robert Music Theory
387932 Mermier, Guy Romance Languages
387933 Sands, Donald English
387934 Shuger, Debora English
387935 Steneck, Nicholas History
387936 Toon, Thomas English
387937 Sitrin, Robert G. Internal Medicine
387938 missing
387939 Horner, Thomas M. Psychiatry
387940 missing
387941 missing
387942 Carpenter, Bodhana Slavic Language/Literature
387943 Bronstein, Paul Psychology
387944 Heady, Judith E. Natural Sciences
387945 Imperiale, Michael Microbiology/Immunology
387946 Marino, Lucyndia Pediatrics
387947 Morganroth, Melvin Internal Medicine
387948 Mostafapour, M.K. Natural Sciences
387949 Palmer, Jeffrey Biological Sciences
387950 missing
387951 Pearson, William Chemistry
387952 Pecoraro, Vincent Chemistry
387953 Sheikh, Kazim Epidemiology
387954 Tosney, Kathryn Biological Sciences
387955 Ben-Jacob, Eshel Physics
387956 Bretz, Michael Physics
387957 Chang, Mei-Chu Mathematics
387958 Groisser, David Mathematics
387959 Hero, Alfred O. EECS
387960 missing
387961 Teneketzis, D. EECS
387962 Teske, Richard Astronomy
387963 Becker, Marvin History
387964 Gelman, Susan A. Psychology
387965 Speth, John D. Anthropology
387966 Suny, Ronald G. History
387967 Allen, Terry History of Art
387968 Cole, Juan History
387969 Gregory, David D. Dance
387970 missing
387971 Hannay, John C. English
387972 Dwyer, Charles M. Art
387973 Loeb, Louise E. Philosophy
387974 Michalowski, P. Near East Studies
387975 Derr, Ellwood Music Theory
387976 Ashe, Arthur III Chemistry
387977 Williams, William EECS
387978 Spink, Walter History of Art
387979 Leonard, Joanne Art
387980 missing
387981 Brown, Wesley M. Biological Sciences
387982 Gallagher, Kim P. Physiology/Surgery
387983 Hill, Gretchen M. Community Health Programs
387984 Hood, Terry W. Surgery/Neurosurgery
387985 Hyneck, Martha Pharmacy
387986 Mancini, William R. Pharmacology
387987 McKeever, Paul E. Pathology
387988 Rizki, Tahir M. Biological Sciences
387989 Weiner, Norman Pharmacy
387990 missing
387991 missing
387992 Bazzi, Ali Natural Sciences
387993 missing
387994 Freudenberg, J.S. EECS
387995 Kelton, W. David IOE
387996 Slezak, Scott E. Mechanical Engineering
387997 Weinberger, Doreen EECS
387998 Anderson-Levitt, K. Behavioral Sciences
387999 Eley, Geoffrey H. History